Ryan Jamison

Full Stack Developer

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Technical professional with a proven record of leadership among diverse individuals in a competitive business environment. Outgoing, personable, and able to adapt well in strenuous conditions. Innovative thinker with entrepreneurial experience. Graduate of University of Pennsylvania Full Stack Developer Bootcamp. Motivated to blend background in entrepreneurship & technical skills to create unique and fluid full stack web applications.

DEMONSTRATED ACHIEVEMENTS

*Created Full Stack Web applications using the latest technologies
*Successfully ran campaign for Committeeperson in 50th Ward
*Planned First Day Fest, an event to bridge the gap between public schools and the community in Northwest Philadelphia. Worked collaboratively with school administration, elected officials, and local businesses to provide breakfast and resources to 4 neighborhood schools.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Javascript, Node.js, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, MySQL, MongoDB, JQuery, Restful API, Git, RESTful API, Adobe Creative Suite.

CONTACT INFORMATION

Telephone: 215-290-5159

Email: ryanjamison26@gmail.com

Website:

https://rdj215.github.io/portfolio/

Address:

8561 Michener Ave., Philadelphia, PA 19150

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

PRESIDENT - JAMISON CONTRACTING, LLC 2012-Present

- Position firm to compete for competitive bid contracts by building a visible brand through strategic partnerships, community outreach, and aggressive marketing.
- Work closely with high level officers throughout procurement process including but not limited to pre-bid meetings, site visits, proposals, and scheduling of work.
- Partner with nationally and regionally recognized entities including SEPTA, Amazon, Philadelphia Water, Philadelphia Job Corps, and Office of Senator Art Haywood.
- Oversee operations to ensure company initiatives and goals are
 met
- Secure funding for operations, negotiate payment terms with vendors and clients.
- Participate in trainings/programs for small businesses

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA

Certificate - Full Stack Developer Bootcamp June 2019

INDIANA UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA

No Degree - Business Administration 2009

WALTER BIDDLE SAUL HS FOR AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES

Diploma - Landscape & Design 2007

OTHER EXPERIENCE

200TH LEGISLATIVE DISTRICT MILLENNIAL ADVISORY COUNCIL

2018 - Present Member

50TH DEMOCRATIC WARD EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE

2018 - Present Committee Person

MILLENNIALS IN ACTION

2017 - 2019 **Board Member**

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST